// Question/Answer objects
const questions = [
    // Question [0]
    {
        question: "What does JSON stand for?",
        falseAnswers: ["Java Syntax Object Notation", "JavaScript Object Nomenclature"],
        trueAnswer: "JavaScript Object Notation",
    },
    // Question [1]
    {
        question: "\"64-bit\" and \"32-bit\" commonly describes.",
        falseAnswers: ["Memory", "Storage", "Refresh Rate"],
        trueAnswer: "Processor Architecture",
    },
    // Question [2]
    {
        question: "Replace the asterisks in the following: ***(let i = 0; i < x.length; i++) {}",
        falseAnswers: ["if", "forEach", "while"],
        trueAnswer: "for",
    },
    // Question [3]
    {
        question: "JavaScript and Java are the same programming language.",
        falseAnswers: ["True"],
        trueAnswer: "False",
    },
    // Question [4]
    {
        question: "The \'fat-arrow\' (=>) is sometimes called a _ in other languages.",
        falseAnswers: ["Closure", "Assembly", "Anonymous", "Callback"],
        trueAnswer: "Lambda",
    },
    // Question [5]
    {
        question: "This language alters a web page aesthetically.",
        falseAnswers: ["HTML", "JavaScript", "JSON"],
        trueAnswer: "CSS",
    },
    // // Question [6]
    // {
    //     question: "",
    //     falseAnswers: "",
    //     trueAnswer: "",
    // },
    // // Question [7]
    // {
    //     question: "",
    //     falseAnswers: "",
    //     trueAnswer: "",
    // },
    // // Question [8]
    // {
    //     question: "",
    //     falseAnswers: "",
    //     trueAnswer: "",
    // },
    // // Question [9]
    // {
    //     question: "",
    //     falseAnswers: "",
    //     trueAnswer: "",
    // },
];